（"神奇发现"）
大家好 欢迎收看"神奇发现"
Welcome, everybody. Welcome to Amazing Discoveries.
又开始了
Oh, oh! It's on again.
各位 拜托别看了
Guys, could we please not watch this?
大家遇过这种事吗 你想好好喝杯牛奶
Folks, this ever happen to you? You go to get a nice glass of milk...
但牛奶纸盒怎么样都打不开
...but these darn cartons are so flinging, flanging hard to open.
天啊 你说的对 麦克
Boy, you said it, Mike.
- 一定有更好的办法   - 没错 凯文
- There's gotta be a better way.     - And there is, Kevin.
- 可以把电视关了吗    - 想都别想 凯文
- Can we please turn this off?     - No way, Kevin.
如果我告诉大家 有一种新产品保证…
What if I told you there's a new product that guarantees...
你不必再打开牛奶纸盒了呢
...you'll never have to open up milk cartons again?
为大家介绍牛奶大师2000
Meet the Milkmaster 2000.
- 有兴趣吗   - 我当然有兴趣
- Intrigued?     - You're flinging, flanging right I am.
这是他的第一次 他没用过这个
This is his first time. He's never used this.
你会看到这使用起来有多方便
You're gonna see how easy this is to do.
- 适用于所有牛奶纸盒   - 好简单
- This works in any milk carton.     - Wow, it is easy. Ha, ha.
现在我每天都可以喝牛奶了
Now I can have milk every day.
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 纵有狂风暴雨 #
# When the rain starts to pour #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 支持一如往昔 #
# Like I've been there before #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
这是正式结果 根本没有好电影可看
It's official. There are no good movies.
我们可以去看烂电影 在电影院里亲热
So let's go to a bad one and make out.
或许你们会希望我转过来 靠着我的背亲热
Perhaps you would like me to turn like this so you can bunny-bump against my back?
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 兄弟 怎么了   - 或许你能告诉我
- Hey, man. What's up?     - Maybe you can tell me.
我的经纪人想知道为什么今天我没有去试镜
My agent would like to know why I didn't show up at my audition today...
数周以来她首度帮我找到的好机会 为什么你没把留言给我
...the first good thing she gets me in weeks. How could you not give me the message?
我可以告诉你 我很享受罪恶感
I'll tell you, I do enjoy guilt...
但那不是我干的
...but it wasn't me.
对 就是他
Yes, it was. It was him. Uh-huh.
好吧 是我干的
Okay, it was me.
- 为什么会是你   - 这真的很疯狂
- How was it you?     - Well, it was all so crazy, you know?
钱德躲在柜子里数到十 但他数到七的时候
Chandler was in the closet counting to 10 and was up to seven...
我还没有找到地方躲
...and I hadn't found a place to hide yet.
听着 我打算跟你说 我都写在手上 看吧 真的
Look, I meant to tell you, and I wrote it all down on my hand. See? All of it.
- 对 那的确是我的试镜   - 没错
- Yep, that's my audition.     - Yeah.
看吧 这就是为什么我会四处放便条纸
See? Now, this is why I keep notepads everywhere.
对 所以我们不找你一起玩
Yep. And that's why we don't invite you to play.
那有什么好难过的 你可以改个时间去试镜
What is the great tragedy here? Get yourself another appointment.
伊斯特试过了 选角导演说我错失了机会
Well, Estelle tried. The casting director told her I missed my chance.
那不公平
Well, that is unfair.
我打电话跟她说那是我的错
I'll call her. I'll tell her it was totally my fault.
你不能那么做 选角导演不跟朋友说话
You can't. The casting director doesn't talk to friends.
- 她只跟经纪人谈   - 她一定过着悲惨的生活
- She only talks to agents.     - What a sad little life she must lead.
好吧
Okay. Ooh.
- 你在做什么   - 不 我知道
- What are you doing? What are you doing?     - No, I know, I know. Ooh.
我是菲比•布非办公室的凯特琳
Hi, this is Caitlin from Phoebe Buffay's office.
安可以跟菲比说话吗
Um, is, um, Anne there for Phoebe?
她会知道是关于什么事
She'll know what it's about.
快挂断…
Hang up. Hang up right...
安妮 听着 乔伊•崔比亚尼有个问题
Annie? Hi. Listen, we've got a problem with Joey Tribbiani.
显然他没去试镜 你是跟我办公室的哪个人联络的
Apparently, he missed his audition. Who did you speak to in my office?
伊斯特 我不知道该怎么处理她
Estelle? I don't know what I'm gonna do with her.
就算你老公跑了 还烧掉房子 日子还是得过下去
So your husband leaves and burns down the apartment. The world does not stop.
有人跟我一样害怕吗
Is anybody else scared?
如果乔伊无法试镜 那都是伊斯特的错 我不在乎
If Joey loses this audition, then that is it for Estelle. I don't care.
安妮 你太棒了 你何时能见他
Annie, you are a doll. What time can you see him?
我需要笔
I need a pen. Pen.
拿便条纸给她…快点
Get the woman a pad. Get the woman a pad. A pad! A pad!
现在你要便条纸了
Oh, now you want a pad.
- 嘿   - 哈罗
- Hey.     - Hello.
我的儿子在哪里
Where's my boy?
我儿子来了
Here's my boy.
他拿着他的洋娃娃
And here's his Barbie.
我儿子拿着洋娃娃做什么
What's, uh...? What's my boy doing with a Barbie?
他自己在玩具店挑的 他很喜欢
He picked it out at the toy store himself. He loves it.
他带着它四处跑 把它当成安抚毯
He carries it everywhere, like a security blanket.
只是多了滑雪靴跟超酷的贝雷帽
But with ski boots and a kicky beret.
对 真的很酷
Yeah, it's cute.
为什么他要买洋娃娃
Why does he have it again?
他买了洋娃娃 有什么大不了的
So he's got a doll. So what?
除非你害怕他长大后会…
Unless you're afraid he's gonna grow up to be...
加入演艺圈
...in show business.
这跟他由两个女人抚养长大的事实毫无关系吧
This wouldn't have to do with the fact that he's being raised by two women?
你们知道吗 没关系 如果你们不反对洋娃娃 我也是
You know what? It's fine. If you're okay with the Barbie thing, so am I.
把洋娃娃交给爸爸 洋娃娃给我 好吧 要不要…
Give Daddy the Barbie. Give me the Barbie. Okay, how about...?
你不想玩怪兽卡车吗
Don't you wanna play with a monster truck?
不要吗 好吧
No? Okay.
要不要玩恐龙战士
Ooh, ooh. How about a Dino-Soldier?
罗斯 你太可悲了
You are so pathetic.
为什么你儿子不能玩洋娃娃
Why can't your son just play with his doll?
我得去上班了
I gotta go to work.
谁看到我左边的咪咪了
Has anybody seen my left boob?
我喜欢那部电影
I loved that movie.
原来在这里 乔伊 你在做什么
Here it is. Joey, what are you doing?
对不起 感觉太舒服了
I'm sorry. It just felt nice.
乔伊 快接电话
Joe. Joe. Answer the phone.
我只剩一只手 你得帮我服务 帮我拿毛衣过来
I only got one arm. You should do stuff for me. Get me a sweater.
快点 是珍妮丝打来的
Just do it. It's Janice.
我一接 今晚就得跟她见面
And if I get it, I'm gonna have to see her tonight.
太棒了 今晚我得跟她见面
Oh, that's great. I'm gonna have to see her tonight.
为什么你不想见珍妮丝
Why don't you wanna see Janice?
昨天吃晚餐时 一上菜
Last night at dinner, when the meals came...
她将她点的柠檬香鸡排一半放进我盘子里 挖走我的番茄
...she put half her chicken piccata on my plate and took all my tomatoes.
那真的很糟糕 因为…
And that's bad...
你讨厌柠檬香鸡排
...because you hate chicken piccata?
不
No.
你不想分享番茄 番茄对你来说很重要
You didn't wanna share your tomatoes. Tomatoes are very important to you.
不是 是突然间我们变成这样的情侣
All of a sudden, we were this couple.
我的脑海里警铃大响
And this alarm started going off in my head.
为了你的人生 快跑 快离开这栋大楼
"Run for your life! Get out of the building!"
男人太难以置信了 珍妮丝以为她给了你鸡肉
Ugh. Men are unbelievable. Janice thought she was giving you chicken.
你们到底是怎么了
What is it with you people?
你们一有感觉就得逃跑
The minute you feel something, you have to run away?
我知道 那…
I know. That...
所以今晚我不想去 我担心我会说出蠢话
That's why I don't wanna go tonight. I'm afraid I'm gonna say something stupid.
你是说男人会装出冷淡无情
Oh. You mean that guy thing where you act mean and distant...
逼我们跟你们分手
...until you get us to break up with you?
你们都知道
Hey, you know about that?
我怎么做我要过这一关
What do I do? I wanna get past this.
我不要害怕承诺
I don't wanna be afraid of the commitment thing.
我要通过隧道 直奔另一头
I wanna go through the tunnel to the other side.
在那里你不会害怕承诺
Where there's no fear of commitment.
大家有…
Do we have any...?
大家有点子吗
Do we have any thoughts here?
我不曾通过隧道 因为…
I've never been through the tunnel myself because...
因为车上只能有一个女孩
...you're not allowed through with more than one girl in the car.
但我觉得这跟其他事一样 面对恐惧
But it seems to me it's pretty much like anything else. Face your fear.
怕高的人就爬到大楼顶楼
You have a fear of heights? Go to the top of the building.
怕虫子的人
You're afraid of bugs.
去抓只虫子来
Get a bug.
对吧
Right?
以现在的情况 你害怕承诺
You have a fear of commitment.
我建议你乖乖出现 成为史上最爱承诺的男人
So I say you go in there and you be the most committed guy there ever was.
没错 那真的很有道理
Amazingly, that makes sense.
- 你们真的那么想   - 对 冲啊 兄弟
- Do you think?     - Oh, yeah. Go for it, man.
从高处跳下
Jump off the high dive.
盯着枪管 逆风尿尿
Stare down the barrel of the gun. Pee into the wind.
乔伊 如果我得盯着枪管看
Joe, if I'm staring down the barrel of a gun...
我会尿得到处都是
...I'm gonna be pretty much peeing every which way.
（中央咖啡厅）
是你今天早上的试镜结果
Ooh, it's your audition from this morning.
我能打一下电话吗
Can I use the phone?
当然 那是电话的功能 供紧急事件跟假经纪人使用
Sure, that's what it's there for. Emergencies and, uh, pretend agents.
加油 宝贝
Come on, baby. Come on.
嗨 我是菲比•布非 请问哪位找
Hi. I have Phoebe Buffay returning a page.
好的 她在车里 我帮你接过去
Okay, well, she's in her car. I'll have to patch you through.
非常聪明
Very nice touch.
好的 请说
Okay, go ahead.
快说…
Talk, talk, talk.
嗨 安妮
Hi, Annie?
太棒了
Fantastic.
- 你被录取了   - 你被录取了
- You got it.     - Oh! You got it.
你问我他是照薪资标准计薪吗
Um, will he work for scale, you ask me?
我不知道
Well, I don't know about that.
我要他那么做 他就得那么做
Except that l do and he will.
太棒了 你真是个甜心
Great. Oh, you are such a sweetheart.
我很乐意跟你共进午餐
I would love to have lunch with you.
我们何不约下…
How about we have lunch next...?
我进隧道了
Oop, went through a tunnel. Ha, ha.
不可思议
Unbelievable.
太谢谢你了
Oh, thank you so much.
这真的很好玩 我是说我没用过汽车电话
It was really fun. I mean, I've never talked on a car phone before.
你真的太棒了 你能帮我一个大忙吗
Oh. You are so amazing. Could you do me this huge favor?
我要参加另一场试镜 但伊斯特始终没办法帮我安排
There's this one other audition I want, and Estelle couldn't get me in.
我不知道 一次还蛮好玩的 可是…
Uh, I don't know. It was fun one time, but...
别这样 拜托 再一次就好
Come on, please? It would just be this one more.
事实上是两次
Well, actually it's two.
- 两次   - 对
- Two?     - Yeah.
应该是三次
Well, really it's three.
拜托 你真的很厉害 我爱你
Please? You're so good at it. I love you.
好吧 就三次 对吧
Okay. But just these three, right?
不 是四次
No, it's four.
为什么今晚你想在家里吃饭
So how come you wanted to eat in tonight?
因为我要…
Because I wanted...
送你这个
...to give you this.
你真的太窝心了
Oh. Are you a puppy!
壁纸贴
Contact paper.
跟你上床的人送你壁纸贴时
You never know what to say when someone you're sleeping with...
你会不知道该说什么
...gives you contact paper. Ha, ha.
等一下 还有一样礼物 看吧 壁纸贴少不了
Wait, there's more. See, the contact paper is to go...
全新抽屉
...in your brand-new drawer.
听着 这是我柜子的抽屉
See, the drawer actually goes in my dresser.
你不必这么做
Oh. You didn't have to do this.
我一定要
Yes, I did.
我一定要 因为你是我的女朋友
Yes, I did. Because you're my girlfriend...
女朋友就该得到那些东西
...and that's what girlfriends should get.
我不知道该怎么说
Oh. Well, I gotta buy a vowel...
因为…天啊
...because, oh, my God. Mwah.
谁想得到有一天
Who would've thought that someday...
钱德宾会送我抽屉呢
...Chandler Bing would buy me a drawer?
我也想不到
Well, not me.
但事实就是那样 还有一件事
But that's what's happened. And, uh, there's more.
我们该去旅行
We should take a trip.
是吗
We should?
对 我们是情侣 情侣都会那么做
Yup. We're a couple, and that's what couples do.
我要跟你爸妈见面
And I wanna meet your parents.
我们该跟你爸妈一起旅行
We should take a trip with your parents.
我想我们不必那么做 因为你吓到我了
I don't think we need to, because you're tripping me out right now.
- 你没事吧   - 我很好
- Are you okay?     - No, I am.
我好得很 这真的太棒了
Ha, ha. I actually am. This is amazing.
我一辈子都害怕这么做
My entire life, I have feared this place.
现在我做了 这有什么大不了的
And now that I'm here, it's like, what was the big deal?
或许我可以说"我们一起住吧" 我也能接受
I could probably say, "Let's move in together," and I'd be okay.
或许你要我们住在一起
You probably want us to move in together?
- 我不害怕   - 对 我害怕得要命
- It doesn't scare me.     - Yeah, well it scares me.
我还没有办好离婚手续 你邀请我来吃意大利面
I'm not even divorced yet. You just invited me over here for pasta...
突然间你说我们得住在一起
...and all of a sudden you're talking about moving in together.
我甚至一点都不饿
And I wasn't even that hungry.
你知道吗 已经很晚了 我该…
You know what? It's getting really late, and I should just, um...
别走 我吓到你了 我说太多了
Don't go. I've scared you. I've said too much.
我无药可救又绝望 渴求着爱情
I'm hopeless and awkward and desperate for love.
嘿 珍妮丝 是我
Hey, Janice, it's me.
我要预先跟你道歉 因为我要跑到街上追你
I wanted to apologize in advance for having chased you down the street.
再见
Bye-bye.
拿去吧 甜心 这应该会有帮助
Here you go, honey. This will help.
我终于追上她 她说
So I catch up to her and she says...
这段关系发展得太快 我们应该放慢脚步
...this relationship's going too fast and we have to slow down.
那不是件好事
gh. That is never good.
然后她说我…
Then I got all...
太黏人 太依赖了
...needy and clingy.
等一下 或许没那么糟糕 你们是怎么分开的
Now, wait a minute. Maybe it's not so bad. How did you leave it?
她说她会打电话给我
She said she'd call me.
天啊
Oh, God.
欢迎光临我们这边的隧道
Ugh. Welcome to our side of the tunnel.
对了 这个冰淇淋好难吃的
This ice cream tastes like crap, by the way.
对 那是低卡脱脂豆浆冰淇淋
Yeah, well, it's that low-cal, nondairy, soy-milk junk.
我们只在无药可救时 才会吃真的冰淇淋
We save the real stuff for the truly terminal cases.
当你常常无药可救时 就得改吃低脂冰淇淋
When you start getting screwed over all the time, you gotta switch to low-fat.
没错
Yeah, you do.
你们不觉得我无药可救
So you don't think I'm terminal?
当然 你不是无药可救 我们只是得做些损害控管
Oh, no, not at all. You're not terminal. We just need some damage control.
好吧 我该打电话给她吗
Okay. Okay. So should I call her?
不
No.
现在是关键时刻 如果你想打电话给她
It's a critical time. If you feel yourself reaching for that phone...
你得去血拼或泡个澡
...you go shopping, you get your butt in a bubble bath.
如果你要她回来 就得开始表现出高傲的样子
If you want her back, you have got to start acting aloof.
她得知道你一点都不黏人
She has to know you're not needy.
你要做的是
So, what you have to do is...
就是故意跟她巧遇
...you have to accidentally run into her on purpose...
装出高仿的模样
...and then act aloof.
那样我就不会失去她
So I'm not gonna lose her?
甜心 你不是个失败者
Oh, honey, you're not a total loser.
我是问我就不会失去她了吗
I said, so I'm not gonna lose her?
看看是谁来了
Guess who's here.
他是玩具王国的超级硬汉 小班
It's the toughest guy in Toyland, Ben.
真正的美国英雄 我是特种部队
Real American hero I'm G.I. Joe
放下洋娃娃…
Drop the Barbie. Drop the Barbie.
特种部队 你真的觉得他会玩吗
G.I. Joe? You really think he's gonna fall for that?
特种部队 酷啊 我能玩吗
G.I. Joe? Cool. Can I play?
看吧 小班 他是保护美国海外石油利益的玩具
Look, Ben. It's a toy that protects U.S. Oil interests overseas.
加油 特种部队
Go, Joe!
哈罗
Hello. Oh.
- 菲比 你来了  - 不 我走错门了 抱歉
- Phoebe, there you are.     - No, it's not. Sorry.
菲比 等一下
But, Phoebe, wait, wait. Phoebe. Phoebe.
乔伊 好吧 你穿那条裤子
Oh, Joey. Oh, okay. See, I didn't recognize you...
害我都认不出来了
...in those pants.
听着 我试镜的那部电视电影 有消息了吗
That TV movie I went in for, did you hear anything?
我想我有机会
I think I got a shot at it.
对 他们打电话来 你没被录取
Yes, they called. You didn't get it.
好吗你没被录取 抱歉
Okay? I mean, you didn't get it. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
没关系 这种事常发生
That's okay. These things happen.
但不该是这样的 你知道吗
But they shouldn't happen. You know what?
你从事一个非常糟糕的行业
You're in a terrible, terrible business.
我不想害你露出那种表情
I don't wanna be the person who makes your face look like that. Ugh.
我没事 看吧
I'm okay. See?
现在你既悲伤又可怕
Now you're sad and creepy.
你知道吗 对不起 我不干了
You know what? I'm sorry. I quit, okay?
不 你不能不干了 你是我最棒的经纪人
No, no, no, you can't quit. You're the best agent I ever had.
听着 当演员你一定会被拒绝 你不能把它视为人身攻击
Look, rejection is part of being an actor. You can't take it personal.
这不是人身攻击 他们说从没看过
Not personal? They said they'd never met an Italian actor
意大利腔这么怪的意大利裔演员
with a worse Italian accent.
他们真的那样说
They actually said that?
对 天啊 你又是那个表情 看吧 我没办法做这份工作
Yeah. Oh, God, there's that face again. See? I can't do this job.
不 所以你非做这份工作不可
No, this is why you have to do this job.
经纪人老是在说谎
Agents always lie.
伊斯特会说 "他们挑了其他类型的演员“
Estelle just says stuff like, "They went another way."
但我可以利用这一点
But this? I can use this.
我可以练习新腔调
I can work on a new accent.
好吧 如果那真的能帮助你 好
Yeah, okay. No. If it helps you, okay. Yeah.
你永远抓不到我 特种部队
You'll never get me, Joe!
不 谢谢
No, thank you.
钱德
Chandler.
哈罗 珍妮丝
Hello, Janice.
你来这里做什么
What are you doing here?
我来买东西
Uh, just a bit of shopping.
你还好吗
How have you been?
你在学英国口音吗
Are you being British?
不
No.
现在不是了
Not anymore.
为什么你会来这里买东西 你根本不住在这个社区
Why are you shopping here? You don't live in this neighborhood.
你在这里等我吗
Were you here waiting for me?
我只是…你知道的
I'm just, uh, you know...
来买派对需要用的东西
...picking up some things for a party.
大麦
Barley?
哪门子的派对会吃大麦
What kind of a party serves barley?
对不起 我的朋友没有你朋友优雅
Well, I'm sorry if my friends aren't as sophisticated as yours.
- 派对在哪里举行   - 就在这里雀儿喜区
- Where is this party?     - Here in Chelsea.
派对主人是谁
Whose party is it?
- 一个女人   - 哪个女人
- A woman's.     - What woman?
雀儿喜
Chelsea.
好 这只有两种可能 要不是你背着我偷人
Either you're seeing somebody behind my back...
那让你成为全世界头号混蛋
...which would make you the biggest jerk on the planet...
就是你假装另结新欢
...or you're pretending you're seeing somebody...
那让你变得超可悲 我想要当场抱头痛哭
...which just makes you so pathetic I could just start crying right here.
你想成为哪种男人
So which of these two guys do you wanna be?
我可以变得跟那个男人一样吗
Can I be that guy?
好吧 我们又被正面拒绝了 很多地方需要改进
Okay, we got some more good rejections. Lots of stuff to work on.
好吧 快告诉我
Oh. Okay. Shoot.
好的 动物园广告
Okay. Um... Oh, the zoo commercial.
- 我没被录取   - 对
- I didn't get it?     - No.
他们说你演起人类非常不像
They said that you "weren't believable as a human being."
你可以加强一下
So you can work on that.
太棒了 还有什么
Great. What else?
外百老汇舞台剧的人说 你很帅 可惜太笨了
Um, the off-Broadway-play people said that you were "pretty but dumb."
不 等一下 抱歉 应该是超级笨才对
No, wait, I'm sorry. That's "pretty dumb."
听着 没关系 不 真的
Oh. Look, it's okay, no, no, no. Really.
听着
Look, um...
我真的很感激你 菲比
...I really appreciate this, Pheebs...
但是我想我得回去跟伊斯特合作
...but I'm gonna have to go back to Estelle.
别误会我 做起经纪人 你比她优秀多了
Don't get me wrong. You're a better agent than she is...
至少跟她在一起我的笨脑袋不会爆炸
...but at least with her, I don't wanna blow my pretty dumb brains out.
对 不 我了解
Yeah, no, I understand.
- 是吗 谢谢 好吧    - 对
- You do? Thanks. Okay.     - Yeah.
抱歉
Sorry.
- 等一下   - 什么
- Wait a minute.     - What?
等一下
Wait a minute.
你编出那些东西 只为了不想当我的经纪人吗
Did you just make all that stuff up to get out of being my agent?
喔 被发现了
Oh, he caught me.
我完蛋了
I am so busted.
我就怀疑会是那样
That's what I suspected.
然后我…你们知道的
And then I just, you know...
丢下那包大麦 跑出超市
...threw the bag of barley at her and ran out of the store.
天啊 钱德 我们要你高傲一点 不是要你当呆瓜
My God, Chandler, we said be aloof, not a doof.
我真的毁了一切 对吧
I've actually ruined this, haven't I?
现在能吃真的冰淇淋了 对吧
It's time for the good ice cream now, right?
- 没错   - 好吧
- Yeah, it is.     - Okay.
你知道吗 一定会没事的
You know what? Everything's gonna be okay.
喂
Hello?
嗨 珍妮丝
Hi, Janice.
你能等一下吗
Can you hold on for a second?
好吧
Okay. Okay.
我该怎么办
What do I do?
我不知道 从来没发生过这种事
I don't know. This is unprecedented.
如果我们做出你做过的事 男人从不会打电话来
If we ever did what you did, a man would never call.
怎么办
Hello?
我知道了 假装你刚睡醒 那会把她气坏了
I got it. Pretend you just woke up. That'll throw her off.
- 爱睡虫   - 对 慵懒一点
- Be sleepy.     - Yes. And grumpy.
你们在…别一直叫小矮人的名字
What are you...? Stop naming dwarves.
喂 珍妮丝 嗨
Hello, Janice. Hi.
我很高兴你打电话来
I'm so glad that you called.
我知道我最近怪怪的
I know I've been acting really weird lately...
那是因为我为你疯狂
...and it's just because I'm crazy about you...
我变得超蠢的 非常害怕
...and I just got stupid and scared...
好几次做出傻事
...and stupid a couple more times.
对不起
And I'm sorry.
真的吗
Really?
Ha, ha. Really?
他太幸运了 如果珍妮丝是男人
He's so lucky. If Janice were a guy...
她已经跟别人上床了
...she'd be sleeping with somebody else by now.
我也爱你
I love you too.
太不公平了
Ugh. It's so unfair.
特种部队
G.I. Joe? G.I. Joe?
我不知道该怎么跟你们说 那是他选的娃娃
Hey, I don't know what to tell you guys. That's the doll he chose.
你做了什么在玩具上沾糖
What'd you do, dip it in sugar?
听着 特种部队来了 洋娃娃得闪一边
Look, G.I. Joe's in, Barbie's out.
如果你们无法接受 那是你们的问题
And if you guys can't deal with it, that's just your too bad.
你干嘛这么紧张 他有洋娃娃 没什么了不起的
What are you being such a weenie for? So he has a Barbie. Big deal.
以前你会打扮成女生
You used to dress up like a woman.
什么
What?
你以前总是会穿妈妈的衣服
The way you used to dress up in Mom's clothes?
你在胡说什么
What are you talking about?
大帽子 珍珠项链 粉红色小手提包
The big hat, the pearls, the little pink handbag?
好吧 那全是你编出来的
Okay. You are totally making this up.
你怎么会不记得
How can you not remember?
你逼我们叫你小碧
You made us call you "Bea"?
天啊
Oh, God.
我从来没有这么快乐过
I've literally never been this happy.
你不是很喜欢唱那首歌吗
Wasn't there a little song?
拜托 天啊 我们想听
Oh, please, God, let there be a song.
我才没有唱歌
There was no song. There was no song.
我是小碧
I am Bea
- 我会喝茶   - 够了
- I drink tea...     - That's enough.
你不想…
Won't you?
你不想跟我跳舞吗
Won't you dance around with me?
我是小碧
I am Bea
我喝茶
I drink tea
你不想跟我跳…
Won't you dance around with...?
罗斯
Ross!